usenext.com 2017-02-24

# UseNeXT and the Usenet: Next Generation Downloading

## We protect your data

### Following Privacy Policy applies to UseNeXT.

To better protect your personally identifiable information we provide this policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way information is collected and used. 

If you have any questions regarding personal data, please don’t hesitate to contact us: 

**Aviteo Ltd.**  
Josephspitalstraße 15  
80331 Munich  
Germany  

**Support:** Contact form

**Director:** Christian Robert Schütze

### 1\. Collected Information

**This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the website UseNeXT.**

During your visit on UseNeXT, cookies are used to personalize UseNeXT according to your requirements and to provide UseNeXT with necessary status information for effective administration and further improvement. If you register, several or all following types of personal information are collected: 

Name  
Address  
E-mail address  
Phone number  
Credit Card/PayPal/Debit Information 

### 2\. Usage of Information

Your given information is used to handle and process your registration and to provide and optimize services for you. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order, process payments, and, if necessary, to process debt collection. You can register for newsletters on our website if you would like to receive further information on our products. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

### 3\. Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access and data security we have put in place appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure your information. This Privacy Policy applies to only to the website of UseNeXT. We do not have any influence on materials or information provided by the usenet. UseNeXT has no responsibility for third parties. Please consider that all commentaries, news, other contributions or information you provide within the usenet or the customer forum is publicly available. UseNeXT has no responsibility for anything you deliberately choose to circulate. 

### 4\. Correction

You can access and change your personally identifiable information after login on UseNeXT. To better safeguard your information, if you want to change your provided payment data, please inform our support via support form or telephone. 

### 5\. Google Analytics use 

Our website uses Google Analytics, a Google Inc. web analysis service (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA). Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, text files that are saved on your computer that allow us to analyse your use of our website. The information obtained on your use of our website using cookies is generally transmitted to and saved on a Google server in the USA. Thanks to the IP anonymisation on this website, your IP address is abbreviated by Google within EU member states or in other countries that signed the agreement on European Economic space. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address transmitted to a Google server in the USA and abbreviated there. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to create reports on website activities for site administrators and to provide other services associated with website and internet use. This information is also transmitted by Google to third parties to the extent in which foreseen by law, or in the event the data is processed by third parties hired by Google. Google shall not connect your IP address with other Google data in any case. 

You can avoid saving cookies using your browser settings; in any case, we would like to inform you that, in this case, you will not be able to fully exploit all the functions on this website. You may also prevent Google from reading the data produced via cookies regarding your website use (including your IP address) as well as their data processing by downloading and installing the specific browser plug-in at ([https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en]()). 

By using this website, you consent to the processing of your data read by Google as per the above methods and for the abovementioned purposes. 

For further information on Google Analytics, please visit: [http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/ ]()

### 6\. Google AdWords and Google Display Network 

Our website exploits online Google AdWords and Google Display Network promotion systems. On this topic, Google guarantees its customers and users’ data privacy. Google AdWords enables a cookie on your computer. The cookie only remains valid for 30 days and is not used to identify personal data. If the user visits certain pages in the AdWords customer’s website and the cookie has not yet expired, Google and the customer are able to recognise the user who clicked on the ad and who was sent to this page. This information is used to create statistics that are analysed in anonymous form. We also exploit these Google AdWords functions to address users on this website to third party websites or internet users with profiles of specific interest, based on their internet use. We do not collect any personal information to do this. In fact, any analyses are used to calculate and evaluate promo ads and do not contain your personal information. Users who do not intend to participate in localisation may simply deactivate the Google Conversion-Tracking cookie in the internet browser user settings. These users will not be included in Conversion-Tracking statistics. Please note that Google has its own guidelines concerning personal data privacy. We may not be held liable in any way for these guidelines and procedures. Please visit Google to learn more about their data privacy terms before using our website. 

### 7\. Survey Tools

Customer satisfaction surveys are carried out using a tool supplied by an external service provider (SurveyMonkey). Please ensure that the provider of this tool implements its own [ data protection strategy](https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/policy/privacy-policy/). Participation in customer surveys is voluntary. The customer survey is configured so that IP addresses or e-mails are not collected automatically. E-mail addresses will not be disclosed to third parties. The SurveyMonkey website uses Cookies. More about the different kinds of cookies used on this Website, please click [here](http://help.surveymonkey.com/articles/en_US/kb/About-the-cookies-we-use).
